<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fawful SteamPunked</string>

    <string name="player1">Player 1</string>
    <string name="player2">Player 2</string>

    <string name="buttonStart">Start</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game_board">GameBoard</string>



    <string name="buttonHowTo">How To Play</string>

    <string name="howToTitle">Rules of the game:</string>
    <string name="rules">At the start of a player\'s turn you have the ability to select any one of
        the 5 pipes in the green pipe queue. Once a pipe is selected, it will be placed on the game
        board and is available to move or rotate. There are also 4 buttons a player can use: \n\n
    1. Add a pipe: adds the pipe that was selected from the queue to the current player\'s path, given the pipe is in a valid location.\n\n
    2. Discard pipe: discards any pipe that was selected from the queue and allows you to touch one
        of the 5 pipes in the queue to change it to one of the other 3 types of pipes
        (used to strategically keep pipes your opponent needs out of the queue). A player can go back to adding
        a pipe if they press the add pipe button before discarding a pipe from the queue.\n\n
    3. Open valve: opens the current player\'s starting valve, resulting in a win if there is a leak free path from the start to the finish.\n\n
    4. Surrender: the current player concedes the current game.</string>


    <color name="green"> #4caf50</color>
    <string name="title_activity_end_game">EndGame</string>


    <string name="buttonAddPipe">Add a pipe</string>
    <string name="buttonDisPipe">Discard a pipe</string>
    <string name="buttonOpen">Open valve</string>
    <string name="buttonSurrender">Surrender</string>


    <string name="buttonNewGame">NewGame</string>



    <string name="badMoveOnTop">Invalid Move: there is already a pipe in that location.</string>
    <string name="badMoveNoConnect">Invalid Move: there is no connection point between this pipe
        and another pipe on your path.</string>
    <string name="badMoveOpponentsPath">Invalid Move: you may not place a pipe on
        your opponents path.</string>
    <string name="badMoveConnectToEnd">Invalid Move: you may not place directly to the end pipe
        without connecting to another pipe.</string>


    <string name="openedValve">Continue</string>

    <string name="titleSet">"\'s turn"</string>

    <string name="winner">Winner: </string>
    <string name="loser">Loser: </string>


</resources>
